http://www.smartlegalforms.com/pages/terms-and-conditions-of-use

Log in
·
Create account
Terms and Conditions of Use
Please Read the Following License Terms of Use Before Using This Web Site.I have read and understood the following:TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND LICENSE AGREEMENT BETWEEN SmartLegalForms. Inc. a Delaware corporation doing business as SmartLegalForms (Hereinafter SLF) and you.SmartLegalForms does not offer legal advice and is not a law firm or law practice. The legal information and legal forms and documents are provided by SmartLegalForms.com and is offered for informational purposes only and is "legal information" as defined by Opinion No. 95-056 (December 19, 1995) of the Attorney General of the State of Maryland. SmartLegalForms.com, Inc., offers legal information that is similar to that provided by self-help law books and legal forms offered for sale through retail outlets.I understand that my situation may be unique, and that the legal information within offered may not fit my circumstances, in which case seeking the advice of an attorney would be advisable. Although every care has been taken to insure the accuracy of the information provided, we do not promise, warranty, or guarantee that the information is correct, complete, or up-to-date. We are not responsible for any errors or omissions in the resources or information available within this Web site.Each form and document should be treated as a starting point and should not substitute for professional legal analysis. The service of the site and each form and document is licensed with the understanding and agreement that we, any content provider, and any author, are not engaged in rendering legal, accounting or other professional services. If legal or other expert assistance is required, the services of a competent professional should be sought. The user assumes all responsibilities and obligations with respect to any decisions or advice made or given as a result of the use of any form or document and for the selection of a form or document to achieve the user's intended results.I understand that SmartLegalForms is not acting as my attorney in any way and that no attorney-client privilege is created by this relationship.Our staff cannot make recommendations for any corrections or changes to documents. Any text which is to be revised or replaced must be identified appropriately and detailed replacement text provided by the customer. In short, our customers have the option of either (a) providing us with detailed exact replacement text or (b) revising the document themselves.These Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Maryland USA, as they apply to agreements made and solely performed therein. Disputes arising hereunder shall be exclusively subject to the jurisdiction of the state courts of Maryland.This Web site exists only in the State of Maryland, and the Web site only performs services within the State of Maryland. You agree that your viewing and use of this Site occurs solely within the State of Maryland, regardless of where your browser is physically located, and that all content and services are located in, served from, and performed wholly within the State of Maryland.DEFINED TERMSIn these Terms:"Disclaimer" means the disclaimer of liability contained in these terms;"Documents" means any legal document downloaded from a Web site (as detailed in these terms);"ESP" means Rapidocs, Ltd. or Epoq Group, Ltd."Guide" the Web site law guide;"SLF" means SmartLegalForms. Inc., doing business as SmartLegalForms"Personal Data" means personal data that identifies you;"Service" means the document assembly service based on the Rapidocs system and other document assembly technologies.;"SmartLegalForms, Inc., " is the operator of the SmartLegalForms.co web site."Terms" means these terms [and conditions];"You" means the individual person who has subscribed or become a member of the SLF Service, and if so indicated below, the immediate family members of such person (spouse and children that reside in the same house or apartment)."Web site" means any Web site operated by SLF.AGREEMENTThis is a binding legal agreement between yourself and SmartLegalForms, Inc. Your use of this Web site and/or your acceptance without modification of the terms, conditions, and disclaimers contained in these Terms constitutes your agreement to all such terms, conditions, and disclaimers. If you do not agree with these terms then you are not authorized to use this Web site.OUR AIMSThe Service is intended to bring to the legal market place a product which has never existed in the past, namely an automated fixed fee document assembly system as a means to document various legal transactions in a price competitive way. As indicated elsewhere in this Terms and Conditions Statement, the legal information and legal documents available from this Web site is not a substitute for the legal advice of an attorney who is a member of the bar of the state where you live.THE GUIDEWhile every precaution has been taken in compiling the Service, neither SLF, nor any contributors to the Guide can be held responsible for any action (or the lack thereof) taken by any person or organization, wherever they shall be based, as a result, direct or otherwise, of information contained in or accessed through the Guide. ANYONE USING THE GUIDE IS RECOMMENDED TO SEEK SPECIFIC ADVICE FROM AN ATTORNEY WHO IS A MEMBER OF THE BAR IN THE STATE IN WHICH YOU ARE RESIDENT BEFORE DEALING WITH ANY SITUATION WHICH MAY BE COVERED BY ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED IN ANY PART OF THE GUIDE OR BEFORE EMBARKING ON ANY COURSE OF ACTION.LEGAL DOCUMENT SERVICELimitations on the ServiceYou can purchase non-interactive legal forms from this web site. SLF will use reasonable efforts to update Documents. SLF believes that the Documents contain sufficient information to provide you with a starting point in the process of assembling a standard legal document. The Documents are not suitable to provide expert legal advice or where any particular transaction will require the Documents to be amended or altered. They should be utilized as a guide only to production of the relevant documentation for the particular purpose ascribed to it.Documents are stored on our servers 30 days following purchase if an individual document is purchased,Title and Ownership; No Commercial use limitation; terms of license(a) No transfer of title. The Web site and Documents, and copies of Documents or the Web site downloaded by you are owned exclusively by SmartLegalForms, Inc., , and are licensed to you as provided for in this Terms and Conditions of Use; SmartLegalForms does not transfer to you title to any tangible copy, or original, of the Documents or any part of the Web site.(b) License: You are authorized to: (i) make use of the Document for your own personal use, or for the personal use of your immediate family members. "Personal use" means that the Document or Web site may be copied and used one or more times in respect of a matter or matters in which You (and/or your immediate family member(s)) are personally involved as a party. You may not use the Web site or the Documents for any other purpose, and all other rights to the Documents and Web site are specifically reserved. You may not remove the copyright notice and any terms of license from any Document or any part of the Web site, or use the Documents for any commercial purpose whatsoever. Ownership and copyright in the Documents and Web site belong solely to SLF. You may not modify, copy, distribute, transmit, display, perform, reproduce, publish, license, create derivative works from, transfer, or sell any information, products or services obtained from this Web site.You may not use this site on a professional or commercial purposes. In other words, you may not use this Web Service to generate legal forms or documents for which you resell for a fee to third parties, other than your immediate family. You agree that if we learn that you are using the Web Service for commercial purposes you will be a penalty fee of $100.00 for each document or form generated for a party, not a member of your immediate family. Commercial licenses for this Web Service are available.Re-use of the documentsWe recommend that you check the Web site regularly to ensure that the Documents are the latest versions before reuse. If they are not and SLF has replaced them with revised versions you are recommended to upgrade to the latest version.Limitation of liability in respect of the Documents:SLF has included within this agreement a disclaimer in respect of its liability in respect of the documents. Please read it carefully as the following are the terms upon which SLF provides Documents to you.DISCLAIMER RELATING TO THE DOCUMENTSPLEASE READ THIS IMPORTANT NOTICE WHICH AFFECTS YOUR RIGHTSIF YOU USE ANY DOCUMENT IN THE SERVICE, IT WILL BE ON THE TERMS WHICH ARE STATED IN THIS DISCLAIMER. DOCUMENTS AVAILABLE ON THE SERVICE HAVE BEEN PREPARED BY SLF. WHILE SLF HAS USED REASONABLE CARE IN PREPARING THE DOCUMENTS, IN THE MAJORITY OF CASES THEY WILL HAVE TO BE TAILORED TO SUIT YOUR PARTICULAR CIRCUMSTANCES. THEREFORE THE BASIS ON WHICH YOU PURCHASE OR MAKE USE OF ANY DOCUMENT IS THAT THE DOCUMENT IS SUITABLE TO BE USED BY YOU IN CONJUNCTION WITH PROPER ADVICE AS TO ITS APPLICATION AND ADAPTATION FOR YOUR PARTICULAR REQUIREMENTS. THE DOCUMENTS ARE NOT MADE AVAILABLE TO YOU ON ANY OTHER BASIS. PLEASE NOTE ALSO THAT THE DOCUMENTS HAVE BEEN PREPARED IN LIGHT OF THE LAWS OF A PARTICULAR STATE AS SET FORTH IN THE DOCUMENT, AND THEY WILL NOT BE SUITABLE IN OTHER STATES OR OVERSEAS. YOU SHOULD NOT USE THEM IF ANY PERSON WHO IS TO SIGN THE DOCUMENT OR THE PROPERTY WHICH THE DOCUMENT DEALS WITH IS OUTSIDE THE STATE WHERE YOU LIVE OR INTEND TO USE THE DOCUMENT.SLF DOES NOT TAKE RESPONSIBILITY FOR, AND YOU AGREE THAT ML IS NOT LIABLE FOR, LEGAL ADVICE PROVIDED BY ANY PERSON, WHETHER OR NOT SUCH PERSON WAS A REFERRAL FROM SLF. ADVICE YOU RECEIVE FROM A LAWYER IS THE RESPONSIBILITY OF THE ATTORNEY OR OTHER PERSON ADVISING YOU.SLF WILL NOT HAVE ANY RESPONSIBILITY AT ALL FOR ANY ALTERATIONS THAT MAY BE MADE TO ANY DOCUMENT AFTER YOU HAVE DOWNLOADED OR ACCESSED. PLEASE NOTE ALSO THAT ANY RESPONSIBILITY THAT ML MAY HAVE TO YOU WILL NOT EXTEND TO ANY OF THE FOLLOWING: LOSS OR DAMAGE WHICH WE CANNOT REASONABLY FORESEE MAY HAPPEN; OR, LOSS OR DAMAGE WHICH CONSISTS OF OR INCLUDES ANY WASTED EXPENDITURE, INDIRECT LOSS, LOSS OF PROFITS OR ANTICIPATED PROFITS OR GAINS OF ANY DESCRIPTION OR LOSS OF BUSINESS.IF A COURT OR ANY OTHER BODY HAVING THE POWER TO RULE ON DISPUTES DECIDES THAT ANY PART OF THIS DISCLAIMER IS NOT REASONABLE OR CANNOT BE ENFORCED FOR ANY REASON, THIS WILL NOT AFFECT THE VALIDITY OF THE OTHER PARTS OF THIS DISCLAIMER WHICH WILL CONTINUE TO BE IN FULL FORCE AND EFFECT.Copyright and trademark noticesThe 'SmartLegalForms' logo, and the 'RAPIDOCS' logo are used under license from ESH and SmartLegalForms, Inc. Other company names mentioned on the Web site may be the trademarks of their respective owners.All contents of this Web site are copyright: ©SmartLegalForms, Inc., as copyright holders. (2016). No part of the site may be reproduced in any form whether electronically or otherwise without the prior consent of SLF, other than temporarily in the course of using the Service or to keep a record of a transaction entered into using the Service.Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.Legal identityThis web service is operated by SmartLegalForms, Inc. If you obtain services from a third party then your contractual relationship is with that third party and not with SLF.Prohibited useAs a condition of your use of this Web site, you warrant to us that you will not use this Web site for any purpose that is unlawful or prohibited by these terms, conditions, and notices.HyperlinksThis Web site contains hyperlinks to Web sites operated by third parties. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. We do not control such Web sites and we can not be responsible for their contents. Our inclusion of hyperlinks to such Web sites does not imply any endorsement of the material on such Web sites.General warranty and liability disclaimer; limitation of liability(a) Warranty. SLF MAKES NO IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, AND HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL SUCH WARRANTIES, INCLUDING ALL WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR WARRANTY OF NON-INFRINGEMENT.(b) Liability. In no event will SLF, be liable for any indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages arising out of or in any way connected with the use of the Documents, this Web site or the telephone support service whether based in contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise. The liability of any of SLF, for direct loss arising out of the use of the Documents, this Web site, and the telephone support service whether based in contract, tort, strict liability or otherwise is limited to the total amount paid, if any, by you to SLF.ModificationsWe reserve the right to change any terms, conditions, and disclaimers under which this Web site or any service offered through it are offered. This right will not affect the existing terms and conditions accepted by you upon making a legitimate purchase using this Web site.Statutory rightsThese Terms will not affect your statutory rights as a consumer.Non transferabilityYour right to use the Web site and the Documents is not transferable without the specific written consent of SLF.Access codes and passwords; no hackingWhen you sign up as a member of SLF, you may be provided a password or other access code to download Documents or otherwise make use of portions of the site that are not generally available to the public. You agree that these passwords and access rights are owned by SLF and that you will not disclose these passwords or access codes to anyone or by any means, and that you will maintain such access codes and passwords securely so that no other person may gain access to such codes.Representation of true intentYou represent that you are using the Web site and the Documents under your own name, and not under a pseudonym, fictitious name or under an alias or similar false name, and that all information you have provided about yourself to ML is true and accurate and not falsified.Disclosure of information; SecurityUnless provided otherwise in SLF's privacy policy, SLF will not provide any personally identifying information to any third party without your consent (which consent may be obtained electronically via e-mail or form fill in on the Web site); provided however that you are advised that in the event SLF determines in its reasonable discretion that disclosure of personal identifying information is necessary to comply with any law, rule order, subpoena, civil investigative request or demand, discovery request or any other legal requirement, SLF may disclose your personally identifying information to comply with such request, and it may be disclosed without prior notice to you. SLF agrees to take reasonable efforts to protect your personally identifying information in the event of such disclosure, provided however, that you agree that ML shall not be liable to you for any claim by you that SLF failed to exercise reasonable care in protecting your personally identifying information. You also acknowledge that, despite efforts of SLF to maintain your information secure, the internet is inhabited by many criminal and otherwise malicious persons who may attempt to crack into SLF's computer systems, and that despite SLF's efforts, such person's may be able to obtain copies of your personally identifying information. You agree that ML is not responsible to you for any inadvertent disclosure or unauthorized access by any third party of your personally identifying information.GeneralThese Terms are governed by the laws of the State of Maryland. You hereby consent to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the State of Maryland in all disputes arising out of or relating to the use of this Web site. Use of this Web site is unauthorized in any jurisdiction that does not give effect to all provisions of these Terms, including without limitation this clause.If any part of these Terms is determined to be invalid or unenforceable pursuant to applicable law including, but not limited to, the warranty disclaimers and limitations set forth above, then the invalid or unenforceable provision will be deemed superseded by a valid, enforceable provision that most closely matches the intent of the original provision and the remainder of these Terms will continue in effect. These Terms constitute the entire agreement between us with respect to this Web site and they supersede all prior or contemporaneous communications and proposals, whether electronic, oral, or written. A printed version of these terms and of any notice given in electronic form will be admissible in judicial or administrative proceedings based upon or relating to these terms to the same extent and subject to the same conditions as other business documents and records originally generated and maintained in printed form.
Search
About us
Customer Support
Team
Terms and Conditions of Use
Privacy
Disclaimer
Guarantee
